

## CONTACT

8

Born 1980 in Florence, SC



(843) 229-1193



levinerjamie@gmail.com



github.com/jamieleviner



jamieleviner.com

## SKILLS

JavaScript

jQuery

VueJS

CSS/LESS/SASS

C#/ASP.NET MVC

Go

Intercom

PostgreSQL

# JAMIE LEVINER

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER

For the past 5 years, I have worked as a full stack software engineer with a concentration on front-end architecture, frameworks, and tooling. I am strongly interested in becoming part of a development culture that improves and enables its people, and I am looking forward to facing some new challenges.

### EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer - ACS Technologies July 2017 - present

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

Software Engineer-Associate - ACS Technologies July 2016 - July 2017

Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

Software Development Apprentice - ACS Technologies August 2015 - July 2016

Making coffee and baking cookies.

Intern - ACS Technologies May 2015 - August 2016

### EDUCATION

B.S. in Computer Science, Minor in Applied Mathematics

January 2011 - December 2014, Francis Marion University, Florence, SC 29501